this is the time known as the great pirate era a countless array of pirates go to battle across
the seas in search of the one piece the legendary treasure left behind by gold roger king of the
pirates monkey d luffy a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit set sail
to become the next king of the pirates as luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles they
capture the unwanted attention of the world government which will use any means necessary
to stop them now this site can't wait to see what kind of adventures up next when a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue the crew will cover path across the grand line to the new world
luffy left the female only nation of amazon lily to rescue his brother ace from execution
by the world government with the help of the snake princess hancock luffy stole away on board a
navy ship headed to the colossal prison known as impel down meanwhile the other straw hats scattered
around the globe by bartholomew kuma faced struggles of their own
her friends whereabouts bridging the islands vicious vegetation
love love beam
i'm starting to worry that we might not survive this trip
you'd think they'd learn by now luffy the food has arrived luffy
hey seems like we should have reached ace by now huh
no i'm afraid we still have a while to go
okay
awesome i'm starving
luffy
would you care for a cup of tea sure that sounds good thank you darling my pleasure oh i'll just brew
some up then so luffy why don't you tell me a little about your friends i don't know a thing
of course you don't have to if you don't want to
i'm just making conversation it's not like i'm trying to dig into your personal life and find out
every little thing about you okay which one should i start with
zoro sanji usopp there's brook frankie nami or robin
nami robin those sound like girls names
they are you're watering the table you know
i'm sorry but i'm afraid you and i can't be together
but why tell me why luffy because i'm already with nami and robin
i don't care i won't give up that easily
you really suck at making tea
a woman
her clothes are so strange she can't be from here
she's alive
are you okay miss
well i'm not really sure
where am i it's cold
you're in tequila wolf it's a country in the east blue
you're shivering do you want to come back to my house
well if it doesn't put you out yes i would love to
keep moving pick up the pace
soren did you go out again without asking us don't risk it child the officers didn't see you right
who's that you brought with you i don't know her doesn't look like she's from here
i found her in the snow she was freezing
she's a drifter
it's more likely she's a fugitive
well at least we know she's crazy
no sane person would want to come here
i can tell when i'm not wanted someplace
it's fine i'll leave
i'll take responsibility for her okay
you're not the only one who lives here child
what do you think will happen if the officers find out we're giving shelter to a stranger
i'll take the blame
you can't reason with that girl
and where do you plan on hiding her
she'll stay in my room
the loft upstairs
she'd be okay up there for a day or two i suppose
don't tell me you're serious
we should turn her in before it's too late and we get caught
it's already too late we've let her into our house
might as well show her some courtesy at this point
you do what you want but keep me out of it
thank you
don't go thinking this is for good
she's leaving once her wounds are healed
you know she's better off getting out of this country as quick as she can
they seem like kind people
yeah
thanks
something about you smells so nice
i'm not wearing any kind of perfume
maybe it's the scent of the outside world
what do you mean by that
well you see i haven't left here since i was born
are you some kind of traveler did you come here from a warm climate
yes i've been traveling the world on a ship
is it a big ship what's the island you came from like and were there any
beautiful birds or flowers there
and was there
soren time to work breaks over hurry up and get ready
i have to go to work now you work this late at night
we work all day every day and all night every night
you should get some rest now but i'd love to hear about your travels when i get
back
sure i'll be right here
sorry
i don't think i can make it in time to help them
i'm sorry did i wake you
soren you're covered in dirt
it's okay
just what kind of work do they make you do here
we're trying to build a bridge
what
this country is nothing but one giant bridge
it's eventually supposed to connect a bunch of islands together the construction has been going
on for centuries now at least that's what the officers say for whole centuries if you don't mind
do you think you can tell me about where you're from you mean my home
the island i'm from is now gone but my true home is on the sea and i've traveled to countless islands
soren
what are these
they're islands from around the world
i drew them all from my imagination since i've never been outside to kill a wolf
but whenever i'm drawing one it makes me feel like i'm there like i'm actually visiting that island
and i forget all about being stuck here
wow these are great
sky island
wait you know it so you mean it's real
yes
and you went there will you tell me all about it
of course
now let's see
i guess i should start at the beginning of our trip
wow amazing i knew the outside world was incredible but i'd never met anyone who'd seen it
in this place they push us around every day and they work us until we're so exhausted that we just
collapse but now that i think about it maybe it's not so bad i mean at least we're building
something that will help connect the world and once the big bridge is finally complete everybody
everywhere will get to see so many beautiful islands whenever they want there's nothing i'd like
more i'll travel all over the world and i'll draw pictures of the real islands i visit
that's a lovely thought will you tell me about the other places you've been sure of course
do you mind if we listen too
not at all
the woman's up in the loft good job let's head in men
hey wait don't forget we made a deal and i held up my end so you have to get me out of this
country nobody move what's going on here it's hung for the stranger get in our way and you will die
what's all the noise somebody ratted us out to the officers they're looking for her
what did we do
you guys need something we've got it on good authority that you lot are harboring a suspicious
woman in this house you know we can't take any chances these days there are too many people out
there opposed to the construction of the bridge now turn her over we don't know what you're talking
about look you're just wasting your time there's no one here now leave us alone we're exhausted shut
up are you okay if you refuse to cooperate with us we'll have no choice but to arrest you and question
you individually i take it you're familiar with our interrogation tactics is that what you want
do
captain i found these
all right and what is this crap islands those are my drawings now give them back
Hm, islands, huh?
Hm.
That is some sick sense of irony you've got there, kid.
Give them back!
Hm.
You want your drawings back?
Then you'd better tell us where the woman's hiding.
What woman?
Now let's try that again.
Where is the woman hiding?
I don't know.
Do you want off, Tequila Wolf?
Cooperate and I'll get you out of here.
Then you can see the outside world in person.
I don't know!
I'm giving you one last chance to fess up.
Tell me where she is!
Look! I don't know!
All you're doing is digging an even deeper hole for yourselves.
I'll make sure you all rot on this bridge for the rest of your lives.
Now take them all in for questioning.
Torture them until they tell us what we want to hear.
And I want the kid to get the worst of it.
Come on, move!
Where is she?
Now clutch!
torture them until they tell us what we want to hear and I want the kid to get
the worst of it come on now clutch what's going on hey you guys
ah stay back I'll shoot put your hands up
please don't hurt me I'm sorry I'm sorry
I got you now she's down here I have her in my sights hurry I need backup she's dangerous
why are you still here didn't you hear him yeah the guy just said he's got the woman
you've been looking for why don't you quit harassing us and go get her
I think you've worn out your welcome here uh captain would you quit standing around
and get down there and cover him yes sir I'm letting you off the hook for now but you
are sorely mistaken if you think I'm going to forget about this
have fun with that sir are you all right
I hope she's okay
tequila wolf is a nation of laborers
the people we have constantly toiling away to build this bridge are criminals from all over
the world either that or they're citizens of countries that refuse to ally with the world
government
on your feet in short they're slaves how much longer until the bridge is complete I have no idea but it's
been under constant construction for 700 years now 700 but for what purpose you don't need to
concern yourself with that now that you're here we're putting you to work so the only thing you need to
worry about is making the bridge got it
like a flower blossoming in the middle of the ocean we now arrive at the Bowen Islands
let's get this exploration party going I will of course be the leader of the group the fearless sniper king
and here's my loyal and trusty crew who sadly couldn't be here today I give up where the hell am I
I don't even know if my friends are alive without me it's doubtful they will be for long in fact I bet
they're crying my name right this instant mm-hmm they're lost without me I better hurry up so I can go save them
just the wind
the one-man crew of the Usopp exploration party must remain ever vigilant and watchful indeed let's go
let's go
I can't take this
I've lonely
hey
is anyone out there
out there
I'll finish don't let this be a deserted island
oh
oh no it's the my heart will stop beating if I'm left alone syndrome
collapse
Collapse?
Hey! There's gotta be someone out there!
Don't be shy! Come out and say hello!
Ah! I knew it!
How are ya?
You're rather energetic today!
Hey!
Ah!
Gah!
Whoa!
Huh?
Gonna eat that?
Are you kidding?!
But you saved my life so you can eat whatever you want!
Thank you, whoever you are!
My name is Heraclesen!
Wow! That's a pretty cool name you got there!
Really? Think so?
I'm Usopp. Nice to meet ya!
Ooh! Is this thing edible? I've never seen this kind of fruit before!
Sure, Usoppin! It's fine!
By the way, you can call me Heraclesen!
Yeah, okay. Heard you the first time.
Well, it definitely smells delicious at least.
Maybe I'll just give it a little lick.
Usoppin!
What the?
Was that thing a plant?
And did it really just try to eat me?
Sure!
They are man-eating plantsen!
Man-eating?!
Huh?
What the hell is this place?!
This is the Swindling Forest, Glymston!
Help! Help! Help!
By the way, you can call me...
Parent!
Zoro arrives at an old castle inhabited by Perona.
Although he is eager to return to his crew, Perona seems strangely intent on keeping him there.
Meanwhile, Brook is mistaken for Satan when a group of cultists believe they've summoned the Dark Lord.
On the next, One Piece! The Friend's Whereabouts! A Negative Princess and the King of Demons!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!